Evil Poison
(...)
DJ Smokey
Presents
Certified Terror Music
This album is terrorism
(Allahu akbar)
(...)
(What's good GeeohhS?)
Yeah
I hope my opps get AIDS
Evil Poison
You want that shit done right?
Then do it yourself
I'm the only boss nigga
Paid it myself
Off in them trenches nigga
Slaving myself
$300,000 nigga
Made it myself (Too many hunnids)
Birthday on the first
They're like, "Neph, why you ain't hype about it?"
I paid 300 bills
Shit, what I like about that?
What you want for your birthday?
I want a new 30
Bitch, who gon' do it for me?
You want for your birthday?
Bitch can't afford it
What you want for your birthday?
Shit
A new foreign
I'm going through some shit
Who the fuck gon' relate?
(For real)
Just cause I got money here
A bitch gon' stay
(Certified Terror Music)
Gucci frames on my face
I don't wanna see shit
Cut em off
They're like, "Damn, Neph can't keep shit"
A couple thousand for the shit
This ain't no cheap fit
You did what?
And seen what?
We're gon' believe that shit
Talking bout love
They don't need love they sell
I love my Glock phone 40
Gucci frames and B.B. belt
(Opp genocide)
Chain cost a lot
You ain't got shit to say to me
My nigga explain it to the Glock
Walking in the spot like Mad Max
Throw bombs over Baghdad
If I don't know your back back
Then get your pussy ass whacked
He a below-the-waist shooter
You always aimin' for the legs
I'm like Shaq
When I'm in the paint
I'm tryna bang on a nigga head
Bet I get the rebound
Opps wanna see me down
I got light heron
And I got that Bobby Brown
He was up, they shot him down
For they call me ridin' 'round
Good on my side of town
He moved OT, he hiding out
Shit feel different with a gun in your face
Oh now you don't got nothin' to say
Real mobster, don't look at my face
When I walk in look the other way
This bill change my mood quick
Y'all shoot this shit we shoot shit
I got lawyer and bail money
The opps wishin' jail on me
Fuckin' those, it smell funny
Put your fuckin' mask on
I been in this trap for nine hours
Gettin' bags gone
I put a slab on
Get his lil' ass gone
Shoot a lot
But you always missin'
You got bad form
(Based Negative Squad)
Niggas ain't gon' never walk again
If they think 'bout runnin' in
When I was fourteen
I fronted UNK once
I never saw that nigga again
I pop pills and drink out the bottle
My bitch bad as fuck look like a model
VIC dope, it make 'em wobble
This weed just came out it's not gelato
If you ain't got no money my bitch will not fuck
Moncler on me official as fuck
You can scan the Moncler tag
On my outfit It go right to the website
Ain't no way my mans gettin' left behind
'Cause I'ma make sure I get him right
One time I fronted a nigga
A dime until he paid me
I couldn't sleep at night
When I got my first pound
I broke it down
Broke a whole pound
Down to nicks and dimes
Squeeze out all the profit, I need every penny
Back to school shopping was JCPenney's
I can still get fly a PC ass
We got Xanax pills, molly and X
We got that dog, got DMX
Beat a nigga ass on stage like ass
Poison Incorporating
(What's good GeeohhS?)
We make the best
Poison
(...)
Terrorists win.